[
  {
    "question": "There a book on the table.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a book on the table."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There an apple.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is an apple."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a jacket in the wardrobe.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a jacket in the wardrobe."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a textbook in the backpack.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a textbook in the backpack."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There my backpack.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is my backpack."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a pencil case in her backpack.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a pencil case in her backpack."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a ruler in my pencil case.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a ruler in my pencil case."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a notebook on the desk.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a notebook on the desk."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a yellow backpack in her hands.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a yellow backpack in her hands."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a green notebook in his backpack.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a green notebook in his backpack."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a red apple in the backpack.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a red apple in the backpack."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There an orange crayon in the pencil case.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is an orange crayon in the pencil case."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a green pencil on the desk.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a green pencil on the desk."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There an English textbook on the table.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is an English textbook on the table."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There an orange book.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is an orange book."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There an apple in the lunch box.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is an apple in the lunch box."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a lunch box.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a lunch box."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a blue pen in the pencil case.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a blue pen in the pencil case."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a pencil on his table.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a pencil on his table."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There one cat.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is one cat."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There one parrot.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is one parrot."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There one pig.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is one pig."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a cow.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a cow."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a duck.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a duck."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a rabbit.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a rabbit."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There pictures of cats on my backpack.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are pictures of cats on my backpack."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There three books in my backpack.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are three books in my backpack."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There five notebooks in the backpack.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are five notebooks in the backpack."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There two pencils in his pencil cases.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are two pencils in his pencil cases."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There four pens in the pencil case.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are four pens in the pencil case."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There a rubber in her pencil case.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There is a rubber in her pencil case."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There ten crayons in the backpack.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are ten crayons in the backpack."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There seven colour pencils in my pencil case.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are seven colour pencils in my pencil case."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There eleven pens on the desk.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are eleven pens on the desk."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There three pencil boxes.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are three pencil boxes."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There eight crayons on the table.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are eight crayons on the table."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There sixteen colour pencils in the box.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are sixteen colour pencils in the box."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There eighteen crayons in the backpack.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are eighteen crayons in the backpack."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There three apples in the lunch box.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are three apples in the lunch box."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There fifteen pencils in my pencil box.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are fifteen pencils in my pencil box."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There three stars on my backpack.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are three stars on my backpack."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There four notebooks on my desk.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are four notebooks on my desk."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There two textbooks in her hands.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There two textbooks in her hands."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There nineteen crayons on the table.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are nineteen crayons on the table."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There three dogs.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are three dogs."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There eleven cats.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are eleven cats."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There twenty hamsters.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are twenty hamsters."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There six dogs.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are six dogs."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There two horses.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are two horses."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  },
  {
    "question": "There three trees.",
    "correctAnswers": ["There are three trees."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"there"
  }
]